crazy-frankenstein.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy - Crazy Frankenstein

This is the web site of Crazy Frankenstein, and is owned and operated by MacasWebWorks. This Policy is effective on January 1, 2010. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

At Crazy-Frankenstein.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by crazy-frankenstein.com and how it is used. 

The material contained on this website do not necessarilly reflect the views of Crazy Frankenstein, the advertisers on Crazy Frankenstein, other Crazy Frankenstein, and Crazy Frankenstein affiliated websites.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Crazy-Frankenstein.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Crazy-Frankenstein.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Crazy-Frankenstein.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to crazy-frankenstein.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Crazy-Frankenstein.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Crazy-Frankenstein.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. crazy-frankenstein.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Crazy-Frankenstein.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We guarantee that all files hosted on Crazy Frankenstein are virus checked and do not contain any spyware, dialers, trojans or other malicious programs. However if any damage is caused to your computer we have no responsibility.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can **contact us**.
